<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LiteraryLark</title>
    <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/</link>
    <description>Recent content on LiteraryLark</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. The Madness Years</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/6/</guid>
      <description>1
The Madness Years
China, 1967
The Red Union had been attacking the headquarters of the April Twenty-eighth Brigade for two days. Their red flags fluttered restlessly around the brigade building like flames yearning for firewood.
The Red Union commander was anxious, though not because of the defenders he faced. The more than two hundred Red Guards of the April Twenty-eighth Brigade were mere greenhorns compared with the veteran Red Guards of the Red Union, which was formed at the start of the Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution in early 1966.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Silent Spring</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/7/</guid>
      <description>2
Silent Spring
Two years later, the Greater Khingan Mountains
&amp;ldquo;Tim-ber&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Following the loud chant, a large Dahurian larch, thick as the columns of the Parthenon, fell with a thump, and Ye Wenjie felt the earth quake.
She picked up her ax and saw and began to clear the branches from the trunk. Every time she did this, she felt as though she were cleaning the corpse of a giant. Sometimes she even imagined the giant was her father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Red Coast I</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/8/</guid>
      <description>3
Red Coast I
Ye Wenjie heard a loud, continuous roar. She didn&amp;rsquo;t know how much time had passed.
The noise came from all around her. In her vague state of consciousness, it seemed as though some gigantic machine was drilling into or sawing through the block of ice that held her. The world was still only darkness, but the noise grew more and more real. Finally, she was certain that the source of the noise was neither heaven nor hell, and she remained in the land of the living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Part II: Three Body</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/9/</guid>
      <description>PART II
THREE BODY</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. The Frontiers of Science</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/10/</guid>
      <description>4
The Frontiers of Science
Forty-plus years later
Wang Miao thought the four people who came to find him made a rather odd combination: two cops and two men in military uniforms. If the latter two were armed police, that would be somewhat understandable, but they were actually PLA officers.
As soon as Wang saw the cops, he felt annoyed. The younger one was all right&amp;mdash;at least he was polite. But the other one, in plainclothes, immediately grated on him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5. A Game of Pool</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/11/</guid>
      <description>5
A Game of Pool
As soon as he opened the door to Ding Yi&amp;rsquo;s brand-new three-bedroom apartment, Wang smelled alcohol. Ding was lying on the sofa with the TV on, staring at the ceiling. The apartment was unfinished, with only a few pieces of furniture and little decoration, and the huge living room seemed very empty. The most eye-catching object was the pool table in the corner.
Ding didn&amp;rsquo;t seem annoyed by Wang&amp;rsquo;s unannounced visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6. The Shooter and the Farmer</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/12/</guid>
      <description>6
The Shooter and the Farmer
The next day was the start of the weekend. Wang got up early and left on his bicycle. As a hobby photographer, his favorite subjects were wildernesses free of human presence. But now that he was middle-aged, he no longer had the energy to engage in such indulgent travel and only shot city scenes.
Consciously or subconsciously, he usually chose corners of the city that held some aspect of the wild: a dried lakebed in a park, the freshly turned soil of a construction site, a weed struggling out of cracks in cement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 7. Three Body: King Wen of Zhou and the Long Night</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/13/</guid>
      <description>7
Three Body: King Wen of Zhou and the Long Night
Wang dialed Ding Yi&amp;rsquo;s number. Only when Ding picked up did he realize that it was already one in the morning.
&amp;ldquo;This is Wang Miao. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry to be calling so late.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;No problem. I can&amp;rsquo;t sleep anyway.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I have &amp;hellip; seen something, and I&amp;rsquo;d like your help. Do you know if there are any facilities in China that are observing the cosmic microwave background?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8. Ye Wenjie</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/14/</guid>
      <description>8
Ye Wenjie
Wang took off the V-suit and panoramic viewing helmet. His shirt was soaked with sweat, as if he had just awoken from a nightmare. He left the Research Center, got into his car, and drove to the address given to him by Ding Yi: the house of Yang Dong&amp;rsquo;s mother.
Chaotic Era, Chaotic Era, Chaotic Era &amp;hellip;
The thought turned and turned in Wang&amp;rsquo;s head. Why would the path of the sun through the world of Three Body be devoid of regularity and pattern?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9. The Universe Flickers</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/15/</guid>
      <description>9
The Universe Flickers
Wang Miao drove along Jingmi Road until he was in Miyun County. From there he headed to Heilongtan, climbed up the mountain along a winding road, and arrived at the radio astronomy observatory of the Chinese Academy of Sciences&amp;rsquo; National Astronomical Center. He saw a line of twenty-eight parabolic antenna dishes, each with a diameter of nine meters, like a row of spectacular steel plants. At the end were two tall radio telescopes with dishes fifty meters in diameter, built in 2006.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10. Da Shi</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/16/</guid>
      <description>10
Da Shi
Shi sat down next to Wang and handed him his car keys. &amp;ldquo;You parked right at the intersection at Dongdan. If I had arrived just a minute later, the traffic cops would have had it towed.&amp;rdquo;
Da Shi, if I had known you were following me, I would have been comforted, Wang thought, switching to Shi Qiang&amp;rsquo;s familiar nickname in his mind, though self-respect made him hold back the words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 11. Three Body: Mozi and Fiery Flames</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/17/</guid>
      <description>11
Three Body: Mozi and Fiery Flames
Wang Miao returned home, stopping on the way to buy a V-suit. His wife told him that people from work had been trying to get ahold of him all day.
Wang turned on his phone, checked his messages, and returned a few calls. He promised he&amp;rsquo;d be at work tomorrow. At dinner, he followed Da Shi&amp;rsquo;s advice and drank some more.
But he didn&amp;rsquo;t feel sleepy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12. Red Coast II</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/18/</guid>
      <description>12
Red Coast II
Ye wasn&amp;rsquo;t given a real job immediately after entering Red Coast Base. Under the watchful eyes of a security guard, she was only allowed to perform a few technical tasks.
Back when she was still a second-year in college, Ye had already known the professor who would end up being her thesis advisor. He had told Ye that to do astrophysics research, it was useless to excel at theory without knowledge of experimental methods and observational skills&amp;mdash;at least, that was true in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13. Red Coast III</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/19/</guid>
      <description>13
Red Coast III
SELECTED DOCUMENTS FROM THE RED COAST PROJECT
These documents were declassified three years after Ye Wenjie told Wang Miao the inside story of Red Coast and provide background information for what she told him.
I.
A Question Largely Ignored by Trends in Fundamental World Scientific Research
(Originally published in Internal Reference, XX/XX/196X)
[Abstract] Based on modern and contemporary history, there are two ways in which the results of fundamental scientific research can be converted into practical applications: gradualistic mode and saltatory mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>14. Red Coast IV</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/20/</guid>
      <description>14
Red Coast IV
&amp;ldquo;Professor Ye,&amp;rdquo; Wang Miao said, &amp;ldquo;I have a question. Back then, SETI was marginalized research. Why did the Red Coast Project have such a high security rating?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;That question was asked during the very first phases of the Red Coast Project, and continued to be asked until the end. But now you should know the answer. We can only be impressed by the foresight of the top decision-maker responsible for the Red Coast Project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 15. Three Body: Copernicus, Universal Football, and Tri-Solar Day</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/21/</guid>
      <description>15
Three Body: Copernicus, Universal Football, and Tri-Solar Day
After leaving Ye&amp;rsquo;s home, Wang Miao couldn&amp;rsquo;t calm down. The events of the last two days and the history of Red Coast, two seemingly unconnected strands, now twisted together, made the world unfamiliar overnight.
Once he was home, in order to escape this mood, Wang turned on the computer, put on the V-suit, and logged on to Three Body for the third time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>16. The Three-Body Problem</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/22/</guid>
      <description>16
The Three-Body Problem
As soon as Wang logged out of the game, the phone rang.
It was Shi Qiang, who said it was urgent that he come down to Shi&amp;rsquo;s office at the Criminal Division. Wang glanced at his watch: It was three in the morning.
Wang arrived at Da Shi&amp;rsquo;s chaotic office and saw that it was already filled with a dense cloud of cigarette smoke. A young woman police officer who shared the office fanned the smoke away from her nose with a notebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 17. Three Body: Newton, Von Neumann, the First Emperor, and Tri-Solar Syzygy</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/23/</guid>
      <description>17
Three Body: Newton, Von Neumann, the First Emperor, and Tri-Solar Syzygy
The start of the second level of Three Body wasn&amp;rsquo;t too different than the first: still the strange, cold dawn, still that colossal pyramid. But this time, the pyramid was back in the Egyptian style.
Wang heard the crisp sound of metal striking against metal. The clashing only highlighted the silence of the chilly dawn. Searching for the source, he saw two dark shadows flickering at the foot of the pyramid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>18. Meet-up</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/24/</guid>
      <description>18
Meet-up
The location for the Three Body players&amp;rsquo; meet-up was a small, out-of-the-way coffee shop. Wang had always imagined game meet-ups would be lively events full of people, but this meet-up consisted of only seven players, including himself. Like Wang, the other six did not look like gaming enthusiasts. Only two were relatively young. Another three, including a woman, were middle-aged. There was also an old man who appeared to be in his sixties or seventies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 19. Three Body: Einstein, the Pendulum Monument, and the Great Rip</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/25/</guid>
      <description>19
Three Body: Einstein, the Pendulum Monument, and the Great Rip
The fifth time Wang Miao logged on to Three Body, it was dawn as usual, but the world was unrecognizable.
The great pyramid that had appeared the first four times had been destroyed by the tri-solar syzygy. In its place was a tall, modern building, whose dark gray shape was familiar to Wang: the United Nations Headquarters.
In the distance were many more tall buildings, apparently dehydratories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 20. Three Body: Expedition</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/26/</guid>
      <description>20
Three Body: Expedition
The chilly dawn revealed a bare landscape. There was no pyramid, no United Nations Headquarters, no sign of the Pendulum Monument. Only a dark desert extended to the horizon, just as Wang had seen the first time he had logged in.
But Wang soon realized that he was wrong. What he thought were numerous stones arrayed across the desert were not stones at all, but human heads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Part III: Sunset for Humanity</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/27/</guid>
      <description>PART III
SUNSET FOR HUMANITY</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21. Rebels of Earth</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/28/</guid>
      <description>21
Rebels of Earth
There were many more attendees this time than at the last Three Body meet-up. They met at the employee cafeteria of a chemical plant. The factory had already been moved elsewhere, and the interior of the building, which was about to be demolished, was worn out but spacious. About three hundred people were gathered here, and Wang Miao noticed many familiar faces: celebrities and elites of various fields; famous scientists, writers, politicians, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>22. Red Coast V</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/29/</guid>
      <description>22
Red Coast V
Since she entered Red Coast Base, Ye Wenjie had never thought of leaving. After she learned the real purpose of the Red Coast Project, top-secret information that even many mid-level cadres at the base didn&amp;rsquo;t know, she cut off her spiritual connection to the outside world and devoted herself to her work. Thereafter, she became even more deeply embedded in the technical core of Red Coast, and began to take on more important research topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>23. Red Coast VI</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/30/</guid>
      <description>23
Red Coast VI
The next eight years were among the most peaceful of Ye Wenjie&amp;rsquo;s life. The horror experienced during the Cultural Revolution gradually subsided, and she was finally able to relax a little. The Red Coast Project completed its testing and breaking-in phases, settling down into routine operation. Fewer and fewer technical problems remained, and both work and life became regular.
In peace, what had been suppressed by anxiety and fear began to reawaken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24. Rebellion</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/31/</guid>
      <description>24
Rebellion
After Ye Wenjie finished recounting the history of her first contact with Trisolaris, the abandoned cafeteria remained silent. Many present were apparently just hearing the complete story for the first time. Wang was deeply absorbed by the narrative and temporarily forgot about the danger and terror he faced. Unable to stop himself, he asked, &amp;ldquo;How did the ETO then develop to its present scale?&amp;rdquo;
Ye replied, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;d have to start with how I got to know Evans&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25. The Deaths of Lei Zhicheng and Yang Weining</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/32/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/32/</guid>
      <description>25
The Deaths of Lei Zhicheng and Yang Weining
INTERROGATOR: Name?
YE WENJIE: Ye Wenjie.
INTERROGATOR: Birth date?
YE: June 1943.
INTERROGATOR: Employment?
YE: Professor of Astrophysics at Tsinghua University. Retired in 2004.
INTERROGATOR: In consideration of your health, you may stop the interrogation temporarily at any time.
YE: Thank you. I&amp;rsquo;m fine.
INTERROGATOR: We&amp;rsquo;re only conducting a regular criminal investigation now and won&amp;rsquo;t get into more sensitive matters. We would like to finish quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>26. No One Repents</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/33/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/33/</guid>
      <description>26
No One Repents
The deaths of Lei and Yang were treated as accidents. Everybody at the base knew that Ye and Yang were a happy couple, and no one suspected her.
A new commissar came to the base, and life returned to its habitual peace. The tiny life inside Ye grew bigger every day, and she also felt the world outside change.
One day, the security platoon commander asked Ye to come to the gatehouse at the entrance to the base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>27. Evans</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/34/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/34/</guid>
      <description>27
Evans
Half a year after her return to Tsinghua, Ye took on an important task: the design of a large radio astronomy observatory. She and the task force traveled around the country to find the best site for the observatory. The initial considerations were purely technical. Unlike traditional astronomy, radio astronomy didn&amp;rsquo;t have as many demands on atmospheric quality, but required minimal electromagnetic interference. They traveled to many places and finally picked a place with the cleanest electromagnetic environment: a remote, hilly area in the Northwest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28. The Second Red Coast Base</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/35/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/35/</guid>
      <description>28
The Second Red Coast Base
Three more years passed. Evans seemed to have disappeared. Ye didn&amp;rsquo;t know if he really was somewhere in the world working to confirm her story, and had no idea how he would confirm it. Even though, by the scale of the universe, a gap of four light-years was as close as touching, it was still a distance that was unimaginably far for fragile life. The two worlds were like the source and mouth of a river that crossed space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>29. The Earth-Trisolaris Movement</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/36/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/36/</guid>
      <description>29
The Earth-Trisolaris Movement
The most surprising aspect of the Earth-Trisolaris Movement was that so many people had abandoned all hope in human civilization, hated and were willing to betray their own species, and even cherished as their highest ideal the elimination of the entire human race, including themselves and their children.
The ETO was called an organization of spiritual nobles. Most members came from the highly educated classes, and many were elites of the political and financial spheres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30. Two Protons</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/37/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/37/</guid>
      <description>30
Two Protons
INTERROGATOR: We will now begin today&amp;rsquo;s investigation. We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll cooperate again as you did last time.
YE WENJIE: You already know everything I know. In fact, by now there are many things that I&amp;rsquo;d like to learn from you.
INTERROGATOR: I don&amp;rsquo;t think you&amp;rsquo;ve told us everything. First, we want to know this: Among the messages that Trisolaris sent to Earth, what were the contents of those portions that the Adventists intercepted and withheld?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>31. Operation Guzheng</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/38/</guid>
      <description>31
Operation Guzheng
&amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t worry,&amp;rdquo; Shi Qiang said to Wang, as he sat down next to him at the meeting table. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not radioactive anymore. The last couple of days they&amp;rsquo;ve washed me inside and outside like a flour sack. They didn&amp;rsquo;t originally think you needed to attend this meeting, but I insisted. Heh. I bet the two of us are going to be important this time.&amp;rdquo;
As Da Shi spoke, he picked a cigar butt out of the ashtray, lit it, and took a long drag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 32. Trisolaris: The Listener</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/39/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/39/</guid>
      <description>32
Trisolaris: The Listener
The Trisolaran data contained no descriptions of the biological appearance of Trisolarans. Since humans would not lay eyes on actual Trisolarans until more than four hundred years later, Ye could only envision the Trisolarans as humanoid as she read the messages. She filled in the blanks between the lines with her imagination.
* * *
Listening Post 1379 had already been in existence for more than a thousand years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 33. Trisolaris: Sophon</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/40/</guid>
      <description>33
Trisolaris: Sophon
Eighty-five thousand Trisolaran hours (about 8.6 Earth years) later
The princeps had ordered an emergency meeting of all Trisolaran consuls. This was very unusual. Something important must have happened.
Twenty thousand Trisolaran hours ago, the Trisolaran Fleet had launched. The ships knew the approximate direction of their target but not its distance. It was possible that the target was millions of light-hours away, or even at the other end of the galaxy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>34. Bugs</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/41/</guid>
      <description>34
Bugs
By the time Shi Qiang entered the door of Ding Yi&amp;rsquo;s home, Wang Miao and Ding Yi were already very drunk.
The two were excited to see Shi Qiang. Wang stood up and hugged the newcomer&amp;rsquo;s shoulders. &amp;ldquo;Ah, Da Shi, Officer Shi&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Ding, who couldn&amp;rsquo;t even stand straight, found a glass and put it on the pool table. He poured some liquor into it, and said, &amp;ldquo;Your out-of-the-box thinking was not helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>35. The Ruins</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/42/</guid>
      <description>35
The Ruins
No one believed that Ye Wenjie could climb Radar Peak by herself, but she did it anyway. She didn&amp;rsquo;t allow anyone to help her along the way, only resting a couple of times in the abandoned sentry posts. She consumed her own vitality, the vitality that could not be renewed, without pity.
After learning the truth of Trisolaran civilization, Ye had become silent. She rarely spoke, but did make one request: She wanted to visit the ruins of Red Coast Base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Author&#39;s Postscript for the American Edition</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/43/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/43/</guid>
      <description>AUTHOR&amp;rsquo;S POSTSCRIPT FOR THE AMERICAN EDITION
A night from my childhood remains crisply etched in my memory: I was standing by a pond before a village somewhere in Luoshan County, Henan Province, where generations of my ancestors had lived. Next to me stood many other people, both adults and children. Together, we gazed up at the clear night sky, where a tiny star slowly glided across the dark firmament.
It was the first artificial satellite China had ever launched: Dongfanghong I (&amp;ldquo;The East is Red I&amp;rdquo;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Translator&#39;s Postscript</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/44/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/44/</guid>
      <description>TRANSLATOR&amp;rsquo;S POSTSCRIPT
When I was asked to translate The Three-Body Problem, I was incredibly honored, but also full of trepidation: Translating another writer&amp;rsquo;s work is a heavy responsibility. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like being asked to care for someone&amp;rsquo;s child.
The act of translation involves breaking down one piece of work in one language and ferrying the pieces across a gulf to reconstitute them into a new work in another language. When the gulf separating the two is as wide as the Pacific Ocean that separates China from America, the task can be daunting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Author</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/45/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Three-Body-Problem/45/</guid>
      <description>ABOUT THE AUTHOR
Cixin Liu is the most prolific and popular science-fiction writer in the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China. Liu is an eight-time winner of the Galaxy Award (the Chinese Hugo) and a winner of the Nebula Award. Prior to becoming a writer, he worked as an engineer in a power plant in Yangquan, Shanxi.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
