<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LiteraryLark</title>
    <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/</link>
    <description>Recent content on LiteraryLark</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>0</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/1/</guid>
      <description>The Project Gutenberg eBook of Hung Lou Meng, or, the Dream of the Red Chamber, a Chinese Novel, Book I This ebook is for the use of anyone anywhere in the United States and most other parts of the world at no cost and with almost no restrictions whatsoever. You may copy it, give it away or re-use it under the terms of the Project Gutenberg License included with this ebook or online at www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;You have had the good fortune of starting in life as a graduate,&amp;quot; explained Tzu-tsing as he smiled, &amp;quot;and yet are not aware of the saying uttered by some one of old: that a centipede even when dead does not lie stiff. (These families) may, according to your version, not be up to the prosperity of former years, but, compared with the family of an ordinary official, their condition anyhow presents a difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/3/</guid>
      <description>Pao-yü&#39;s face was covered with the traces of tears. &amp;quot;All my cousins here, senior as well as junior,&amp;quot; he rejoined, as he sobbed, &amp;quot;have no gem, and if it&#39;s only I to have one, there&#39;s no fun in it, I maintain! and now comes this angelic sort of cousin, and she too has none, so that it&#39;s clear enough that it is no profitable thing.&amp;quot;
Dowager lady Chia hastened to coax him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/4/</guid>
      <description>After this followed a picture of several streaks of fleeting clouds, and of a creek whose waters were exhausted, with the text:
Riches and honours too what benefit are they?
In swaddling clothes thou&#39;lt be when parents pass away;
The rays will slant, quick as the twinkle of an eye;
The Hsiang stream will recede, the Ch&#39;u clouds onward fly!\
Then came a picture of a beautiful gem, which had fallen into the mire, with the verse:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/5/</guid>
      <description>Lady Feng smiled. &amp;quot;Do pray sit down,&amp;quot; she said, &amp;quot;and listen to what I&#39;m going to tell you. What you, old lady, meant a little while back to convey, I&#39;m already as much as yourself well acquainted with! Relatives, as we are, we shouldn&#39;t in fact have waited until you came to the threshold of our doors, but ought, as is but right, to have attended to your needs. But the thing is that, of late, the household affairs are exceedingly numerous, and our lady, advanced in years as she is, couldn&#39;t at a moment, it may possibly be, bethink herself of you all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/6/</guid>
      <description>Pao Ch&#39;ai too could not suppress a smile, and as she pinched Tai-yü&#39;s cheek, she exclaimed, &amp;quot;Oh the tongue of this frowning girl! one can neither resent what it says, nor yet listen to it with any gratification!&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Don&#39;t be afraid!&amp;quot; Mrs. Hsüeh went on to say, &amp;quot;don&#39;t be afraid; my son, you&#39;ve come to see me, and although I&#39;ve nothing good to give you, you mustn&#39;t, through fright, let the trifle you&#39;ve taken lie heavy on your stomach, and thus make me uneasy; but just drink at your pleasure, and as much as you like, and let the blame fall on my shoulders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/7/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;Why need you be so modest?&amp;quot; observed Chia Chen; &amp;quot;Doctor, do please walk in at once to see our son&#39;s wife, for I look up, with full reliance, to your lofty intelligence to dispel my solicitude!&amp;quot;
Chia Jung forthwith walked in with him. When they reached the inner apartment, and he caught sight of Mrs. Ch&#39;in, he turned round and asked Chia Jung, &amp;quot;This is your honourable spouse, isn&#39;t it?&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/8/</guid>
      <description>Tai-ju and his wife wept bitterly for him, to the utter disregard of their own lives, while in violent terms they abused the Taoist priest. &amp;quot;What kind of magical mirror is it?&amp;quot; they asked. &amp;quot;If we don&#39;t destroy this glass, it will do harm to not a few men in the world!&amp;quot;
Having forthwith given directions to bring fire and burn it, a voice was heard in the air to say, &amp;quot;Who told you to look into the face of it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/9/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;My daughter&#39;s funeral has,&amp;quot; observed Chia Chen, &amp;quot;put your Highness to the trouble of coming, an honour which we, though noble by birth, do not deserve.&amp;quot;
Shih Jung smiled. &amp;quot;With the terms of friendship,&amp;quot; he added, &amp;quot;which have existed for so many generations (between our families), is there any need for such apologies?&amp;quot;
Turning his head round there and then, he gave directions to the senior officer of his household to preside at the sacrifices and to offer libations in his stead; and Chia She and the others stood together on one side and made obeisance in return, and then came in person again and gave expression to their gratitude for his bounty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/10/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;Don&#39;t talk nonsense!&amp;quot; replied lady Feng laughing; &amp;quot;I&#39;ve found no place, as yet, where I could put away all my own things; and do the stealthy practices of you people take my fancy?&amp;quot;
As she uttered these words she straightway went her way.
Chia Se, at this time, likewise, asked Chia Lien: &amp;quot;If you want anything (in the way of curtains), I can conveniently have them woven for you, along with the rest, and bring them as a present to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/11/</guid>
      <description>Pao-yü could not refrain from approaching her. &amp;quot;My dear cousin, my own cousin,&amp;quot; he added, &amp;quot;I confess my fault!&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Go and find Pao-yü!&amp;quot; dowager lady Chia thereupon gave a shout from where she was in the front apartment, and all the attendants explained that he was in Miss Lin&#39;s room.
&amp;quot;All right, that will do! that will do!&amp;quot; her ladyship rejoined, when she heard this reply; &amp;quot;let the two cousins play together; his father kept him a short while back under check, for ever so long, so let him have some distraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/12/</guid>
      <description>Hua Tzu-fang, upon hearing that there was good reason in what he said, promptly clasped Pao-yü out of the chair and put him on the horse, whereupon after Pao-yü smilingly remarked: &amp;quot;Excuse me for the trouble I&#39;ve surely put you to,&amp;quot; they forthwith entered again by the back gate; but putting aside all details, we will now confine ourselves to Pao-yü.
After he had walked out of the door, the several waiting-maids in his apartments played and laughed with greater zest and with less restraint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/13/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER XXI. The eminent Hsi Jen, with winsome ways, rails at Pao-yü, with a view
to exhortation.
The beauteous P&#39;ing Erh, with soft words, screens Chia Lien.\
But to resume our story. When Shih Hsiang-yün ran out of the room, she was all in a flutter lest Lin Tai-yü should catch her up; but Pao-yü, who came after her, readily shouted out, &amp;quot;You&#39;ll trip and fall. How ever could she come up to you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/14/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;This one devised by Mr. Tertius,&amp;quot; the eunuch was further heard to say, &amp;quot;is not properly done; and as Her Majesty herself has been unable to guess it she commanded me to bring it back, and ask Mr. Tertius what it is about.&amp;quot;
After the party had listened to these words, they all pressed forward to see what had been written. The burden of it was this:
The elder brother has horns only eight;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>14</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/The-Story-of-the-Stone/15/</guid>
      <description>Ni Erh gave a broad grin. &amp;quot;It&#39;s only fifteen taels and three mace,&amp;quot; he answered, &amp;quot;and if you insist upon writing an I.O.U., I won&#39;t then lend it to you!&amp;quot;
Chia Yün at these words, took over the money, smiling the while. &amp;quot;I&#39;ll readily,&amp;quot; he retorted, &amp;quot;comply with your wishes and have done; for what&#39;s the use of exasperating you!&amp;quot;
&amp;quot;Well then that will be all right!&amp;quot; Ni Erh laughed; &amp;quot;but the day is getting dark; and I shan&#39;t ask you to have a cup of tea or stand you a drink, for I&#39;ve some small things more to settle.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
