<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LiteraryLark</title>
    <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/</link>
    <description>Recent content on LiteraryLark</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 1</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/2/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 1 The Divine Root Conceives and the Spring Breaks Forth As the Heart&amp;rsquo;s Nature Is Cultivated, the Great Way Arises Before Chaos was divided, Heaven and Earth were one; Al was a shapeless blur, and no men had appeared.
Once Pan Gu destroyed the Enormous Vagueness
The separation of clear and impure began.
Living things have always tended towards humanity; From their creation al beings improve.
If you want to know about Creation and Time,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 2</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/3/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 2 He Becomes Aware of the Wonderful Truth of Enlightenment By Kil ing the Demon He Realizes His Spirit-Nature The story goes on to tel how after being given a name the Handsome Monkey King jumped for joy and bowed to Subhuti to express his thanks.
The Patriarch then ordered the others to take Sun Wukong out through the double doors and teach him how to sprinkle and sweep the floor, answer orders, and deport himself properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 3</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/4/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 3 The Four Seas and Thousand Mountains Al Submit In the Ninth Hel the Tenth Category Is Struck Of the Register We have related how the Handsome Monkey King returned home in glory, bringing a large sword he had captured when he kil ed the Demon King of Confusion. From then on they practiced the military arts every day. He asked the lit le monkeys to cut down bamboo to make spears, carve swords out of wood, and learn to use banners and whistles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 4</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/5/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 4 Dissatisfied at Being Appointed Protector of the Horses Not Content with the Title of Equal of Heaven The Great White Planet left the depths of the cave with the Handsome Monkey King, and they ascended together on their clouds.As Sun Wukong&amp;rsquo;s somersault cloud was exceptional y fast he reached the Southern Gate of Heaven first, leaving the Great White planet far behind. Just as he was put ing away his cloud to go in, his way was barred by the Heavenly Guardian 50</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 5</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/6/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 5 After Chaos Among the Peaches the Great Sage Steals the Pil s In the Revolt Against Heaven the Gods Capture the Demons The story goes on to relate that the Great Sage Equaling Heaven, a mere monkey devil after al , was quite satisfied that his name was on the register of office without caring about the grading of his job and his own rank, or the size of his salary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 6</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/7/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 6 Guanyin Comes to the Feast and Asks the Reason Why The Lit le Sage Uses His Might to Subdue the Great Sage We shal leave for the moment the Heavenly Generals making their encirclement and the soundly sleeping Great Sage. The story goes on to tel how the Compassionate and Merciful Miraculous Savior from Suffering, the Bodhisat va Guanyin of Mount Potaraka in the Southern Sea, having been invited by the Queen Mother to the Peach Banquet, went to the precious pavilions at the Jade Pool with her great disciple Huian the Novice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 7</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/8/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 7 The Great Sage Escapes from the Eight Trigrams Furnace The Mind-Ape Is Fixed Beneath Five Elements Mountain Wealth and honour, glory and fame,
Are predetermined by fate:
No one should act against conscience to covet any of them.
Far-going and deep
Are the good results of true enlightenment and loyalty.
Heaven punishes al wild and wicked deeds
If not at once then later on.
Ask the Lord of the East the reason why</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 8</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/9/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 8 Our Buddha Creates the Scriptures and Passes on Perfect Bliss Guanyin Obeys a Decree and Goes to Chang&amp;rsquo;an If you try to ask about the dhyana
Or investigate the innumerable
You wil waste your life and achieve nothing.
Polishing bricks to make mirrors,
Or piling up snow to turn it into grain&amp;mdash;
However many years have you wasted like that?
A hair can contain an ocean,
A mustard-seed can hold a mountain,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 9</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/10/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 9 Chen Guangrui Comes to Grief on His Way to His Post The Monk of the River Current Avenges His Parents The story goes on to tel that Chang&amp;rsquo;an city in the great land of Shaanxi had been a place where emperors and kings had made their capitals for generation after generation. Ever since the Zhou, Qin and Han dynasties, the Three Prefectures had been as rich as brocade, and the eight rivers had flowed round its wal s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 10</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/11/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 10 With a Stupid Plan the Dragon King Breaks the Laws of Heaven Minister Wei Sends a Let er to an Of icer of Hel We shal not discuss how Chen Guangrui performed his duties or Xuanzang cultivated his conduct; instead we shal talk about two wise men who lived beside the banks of the River Jing outside the city of Chang&amp;rsquo;an. One was an old fisherman cal ed Zhang Shao and the other was a woodcut er cal ed Li Ding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 11</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/12/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 11 After Touring the Underworld, Taizong Returns to Life.
By Presenting a Pumpkin Liu Quan Continues His Marriage A hundred years flow by like water;
A lifetime&amp;rsquo;s career is no more than a bubble, 163
The face that yesterday was the color of peach-blossom Today is edged with snow.
When the white ants&amp;rsquo; line of bat le col apses, al is il usion;
&amp;ldquo;Repent, repent,&amp;rdquo; is the cuckoo&amp;rsquo;s urgent cal .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 12</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/13/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 12 The Tang Emperor Keeps Faith and Holds a Great Mass Guanyin Appears to the Reincarnated Golden Cicada When the devil officers left the underworld with Liu Quan and his wife, a dark and whirling wind blew them straight to the great capital Chang&amp;rsquo;an, where Liu Quan&amp;rsquo;s soul was sent to the Golden Pavilion and Li Cuilian&amp;rsquo;s to an inner courtyard of the palace, where Princess Yuying could be seen walking slowing beside some moss under the shade of some blossoming trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 13</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/14/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 13 He Fal s into the Tiger&amp;rsquo;s Den and Is Saved by the Planet Venus On Double-Forked Peak Boqin Entertains the Priest The Great Tang Emperor issued an edict
Sending Sanzang to learn the Dhyana teachings.
With firmness and patience he seeks the dragon&amp;rsquo;s lair, Determined to carry on til he climbs the Vulture Peak.
On his long journey he wil visit many a country; Thousands of cloud-capped mountains lie before him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 14</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/15/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 14 The Mind-Ape Returns to Truth The Six Bandits Disappear Without Trace
Buddha is the mind, the mind is Buddha,
Mind and Buddha have always needed things.
When you know that there are no things and no mind Then you are a Buddha with a true mind and a Dharma body.
A Dharma-bodied Buddha has no form;
A single divine light contains the ten thousand images.
The bodiless body is the true body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 15</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/16/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 15 On the Coiled Snake Mountain the Gods Give Secret Help In the Eagle&amp;rsquo;s Sorrow Gorge the Thought-Horse Is Reined in Monkey looked after the Tang Priest as they headed West. They had been travel ing for several days in the twelfth month of the year, with its freezing North winds and biting cold. Their path wound along overhanging precipices and steep cliffs, and they crossed range after range of dangerous mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 16</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/17/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 16 The Monks of the Guanyin Monastery Plot to Take the Treasure The Monster of the Black Wind Mountain Steals the Cassock The master whipped on his horse and hurried straight to the temple gate with his disciple to have a look. They saw that it was indeed a monastery: Hal upon hal ,
Cloister after cloister.
Beyond the triple gates
Countless coloured clouds are massed;
Before the Hal of Five Blessings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 17</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/18/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 17 Brother Monkey Makes Trouble on the Black Wind Mountain Guanyin Subdues the Bear Spirit
As Monkey leapt up with a somersault, the senior and junior monks, the novices, the page-boys, and the servants of the monastery al bowed low to the sky and said, &amp;ldquo;Master, you must be a cloud-riding Immortal come down from Heaven. No wonder that fire can&amp;rsquo;t burn you. Damn that stupid old skinflint of ours: he destroyed himself with his own scheming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 18</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/19/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 18 The Tang Priest Is Rescued in the Guanyin Temple 288
The Great Sage Removes a Monster from Gao Vil age Taking his leave of the Bodhisat va, Monkey brought his cloud in to land, hung the cassock on a nanmu tree, pul ed out his cudgel, charged into the Black Wind Cave, and found not a single goblin inside. This was because the appearance of the Bodhisat va in her true form had so terrified them that they had fled in al directions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 19</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/20/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 19 In the Cloud Pathway Cave Sun Wukong Wins over Zhu Bajie On Pagoda Mountain Xuanzang Receives the Heart Sutra The monster shot forward as a stream of sparks, with the Great Sage behind him on his coloured cloud. As he was racing along, Monkey saw a tal mountain appear in front of them. Here the monster put himself together again by reassembling the sparks, rushed into a cave, and came out with a nine-pronged rake in his hand to do bat le.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 20</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/21/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 20 The Tang Priest Meets Trouble on the Yel ow Wind Ridge Pig Wins Mastery Halfway up the Mountain
The Dharma is born in the mind,
And in turn is destroyed by the mind.
Who do life and death come from?
Decide for yourself.
If it is al from your own mind,
Why do you need others to tel you?
Al you need to do is work hard,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 21</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/22/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 21 The Protectors of the Faith Build a Farm for the Great Sage Lingji from Sumeru Pacifies the Wind Devil The fifty pet y devils fled routed into the cave, their banners and drums smashed, to report, &amp;ldquo;Your Majesty, the Tiger of the Vanguard is no match for the hairy-faced monk, who chased him down the mountain.&amp;rdquo; The old fiend was very angry at the news, and he sat silent with his head bowed as he thought over what to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 22</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/23/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 22 Pig Fights a Great Bat le in the Flowing Sands River Moksa Obeys the Dharma and Wins Friar Sand Over The story tel s how the Tang Priest and his two disciples escaped from their troubles and pressed forward. Before long they had crossed the Yel ow Wind Ridge and were heading West across a plain. The time passed rapidly, and summer gave way to autumn. Cold cicadas sang in moulting wil ow trees, and the Great Fire Star sank below the Western horizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 23</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/24/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 23 Sanzang Does Not Forget the Basic
The Four Holy Ones Have Their Piety Tested Long is the road as they travel West;
In the rustling autumn breeze the frost-kil ed flowers fal .
The cunning ape is firmly chained&amp;mdash;do not untie him; The wicked horse is tightly reined&amp;mdash;don&amp;rsquo;t whip him on.
The Mother of Wood and Father of Metal were original y combined; Between the Yel ow Mother and the Red Babe there was no difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 24</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/25/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 24 On the Mountain of Infinite Longevity a Great Immortal Entertains an Old Friend
In the Wuzhuang Temple Monkey Steals Manfruit The three of them went into the wood and saw the idiot tied up under a tree, yel ing and howling in unbearable pain. Monkey went over to him and said with a laugh, &amp;ldquo;What a son-in-law! So late, and you stil haven&amp;rsquo;t got up to thank your mother-in-law or come to tel the good news to the master.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 25</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/26/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 25 The Immortal Zhen Yuan Captures the Pilgrim Priest Monkey Makes Havoc in the Wuzhuang Temple
&amp;ldquo;The meal is cooked,&amp;rdquo; the three disciples said as they entered the hal , &amp;ldquo;what did you cal us for?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not asking about the meal, disciples,&amp;rdquo; said Sanzang. &amp;ldquo;This temple has things cal ed manfruit or something that look like babies. Which of you stole and ate some?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know anything about it, honest I don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;mdash;I never saw any,&amp;rdquo; said Pig.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 26</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/27/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 26 Sun Wukong Looks for the Formula in the Three Islands Guanyin Revives the Tree with a Spring of Sweet Water As the poem goes,
When living in the world you must be forbearing; Patience is essential when training oneself.
Although it&amp;rsquo;s often said that violence is good business, Think before you act, and never bul y or be angry.
True gentlemen who never strive are famed for ever; The virtue-loving sages are renowned to this day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 27</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/28/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 27 The Corpse Fiend Thrice Tricks Tang Sanzang The Holy Monk Angrily Dismisses the Handsome Monkey King At dawn the next day Sanzang and his three disciples packed their things before set ing off. Now that Master Zhen Yuan had made Monkey his sworn brother and was finding him so congenial, he did not want to let him go, so he entertained him for another five or six days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 28</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/29/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 28 On the Mountain of Flowers and Fruit the Devils Rise Sanzang Meets a Monster in the Black Pine Forest The Great Sage was gazing at the Eastern Ocean, sighing sadly at being driven away by the Tang Priest. &amp;ldquo;I haven&amp;rsquo;t been this way for five hundred years,&amp;rdquo; he said. As he looked at the sea,
Vast were the misty waters,
Boundless the mighty waves.
The vast and misty waters stretched to the Milky Way; The boundless and mighty waves were linked to the earth&amp;rsquo;s arteries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 29</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/30/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 29 Sanzang, Delivered, Crosses a Border
A Grateful Pig Tours Mountains and Forests A poem says
If wild thoughts are not firmly suppressed
There is no point in seeking for the Truth;
If you wish to cultivate your nature before the Buddha, Why stay halfway between awakening and confusion?
Once awakened you can achieve the Right in an instant; The confused wil drift for ten thousand aeons.
If you can invoke the Buddha and cultivate the Truth, Sins countless as the Ganges sands can be wiped out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 30</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/31/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 30 An Evil Monster Harms the True Law
The Mind-Horse Remembers the Heart-Ape
Now that he had tied up Friar Sand, the monster did not kil him, hit him, or even swear at him. Instead he raised his sword and thought, &amp;ldquo;Coming from so great a country the Tang priest must have a sense of propriety&amp;mdash;he can&amp;rsquo;t have sent his disciples to capture me after I spared his life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 31</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/32/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/32/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 31 Pig Moves the Monkey King Through
His Goodness
Sun the Novice Subdues the Ogre Through Cunning They swore to become brothers,
And the dharma brought them back to their true nature.
When metal and Wood were tamed, the True Result could be achieved; The Mind-Ape and the Mother of Wood combined to make the elixir.
Together they would climb to the World of Bliss, And share the same branch of the faith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 32</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/33/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/33/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 32 On Flat-Top Mountain the Duty God Delivers a Message In Lotus Flower Cave Pig Runs into Trouble The story tel s how after Monkey had rejoined the Tang Priest the four of them headed West, united in their shared determination. The king of Elephantia had escorted them beyond his capital to thank them for bringing back his daughter. From there they traveled on, eating when hungry and drinking when thirsty, moving by day and resting at night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 33</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/34/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/34/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 33 Heterodoxy Confuses the True Nature The Primal Deity Helps the Original Heart Taking Pig into the cave the monster said, &amp;ldquo;Here&amp;rsquo;s one, brother.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Let me have a look at him,&amp;rdquo; said the older demon with delight.
&amp;ldquo;Isn&amp;rsquo;t this the one?&amp;rdquo; asked the younger demon.
&amp;ldquo;No,&amp;rdquo; the other replied, &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rsquo;ve caught the wrong one. He&amp;rsquo;s useless.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Your Majesty,&amp;rdquo; said Pig, taking his chance, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m just a useless monk, so let me go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 34</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/35/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/35/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 34 The Demon King&amp;rsquo;s Cunning Causes the Mind-Ape Trouble The Great Sage Wins the Treasures Through Improvisation With the imitation gourd in their hands the two lit le devils were quarrel ing over who should examine it when they looked up and saw that Monkey had disappeared. &amp;ldquo;Brother,&amp;rdquo; said Skilful Beast, &amp;ldquo;even immortals tel lies sometimes. He said that when we&amp;rsquo;d swapped the treasures he would make us into immortals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 35</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/36/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/36/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 35 The Power of Heterodoxy Oppresses the True Nature The Mind-Ape Wins the Treasures and Beats the Demons Lucid the true nature; the Way explains itself; With one turn one jumps out of the net.
To learn transformations is very hard indeed; To become immortal is no common deed.
Pure yields to foul and foul to pure as fate&amp;rsquo;s wheel turns: Break through the kalpas and travel freely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 36</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/37/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/37/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 36 When the Mind-Ape Stands Correct Al Evil Causes Submit When the Side-Gate Is Smashed the Moon Appears in Its Brightness The story tel s how Sun the Novice brought his cloud down to land and told the master and his fel ow-disciples al about the Bodhisat va borrowing the two servant lads and Lord Lao recovering his treasures. Sanzang expressed his thanks at great length, then with great determination and pious sincerity prepared to head West for al he was worth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 37</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/38/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/38/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 37 The Royal Ghost Visits the Tang Priest at Night Wukong&amp;rsquo;s Magic Transformation Lures the Boy Sanzang sat in the meditation hal of the Precious Wood Monastery reading the Litany of Emperor Wu of Liang and the Peacock Sutra until the third watch, when he final y put the scriptures back into their bags. Just when he was about to go to bed he heard a rushing noise and the whistling of a fiendish wind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 38</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/39/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/39/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 38 Questioning His Mother, the Boy Sorts Right from Wrong When Metal and Wood Join in the Mystery, Truth and Falsehood Are Clear 589
If you speak only of the causation arising from birth, You can be present at the Buddha&amp;rsquo;s assembly.
The Buddha of the dusty world thinks only peaceful thoughts; People of al quarters watch while the spirit is subdued.
If you wish to know who is the true monarch,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 39</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/40/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/40/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 39 A Pil of Red Cinnabar Is Brought from Heaven After Three Years the Monarch Is Revived
The story tel s how the Great Sage Sun, his head aching unbearably, pleaded with his master: &amp;ldquo;Stop, stop, I&amp;rsquo;l bring him back to life.&amp;rdquo; When Sanzang asked how, Monkey replied, &amp;ldquo;The only way is to go to the Underworld, find out which of the kings down there has his soul, and ask for it back to revive him with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 40</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/41/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/41/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 40 The Boy Fools with Transformations, Disturbing the Dhyana Heart Ape and Horse Return with a Knife; the Mother of Wood Is Empty The story goes on to tel how the Great Sage Monkey and his two fel ow-disciples landed their clouds and went straight into the palace. Here monarch, ministers, queen and prince bowed to them in thanks, a group at a time, and Monkey told everyone the story of how Manjusri had recovered the demon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 41</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/42/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/42/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 41 The Mind-Ape Is Defeated by Fire
The Mother of Wood Is Captured by a Demon Good and evil are quickly forgot en,
Flowering and fading are of no concern.
When perception is half-revealed it may sink or swim; Fol ow fate and take your food and drink when they come.
Divine peace is stil and solitary;
Stupidity is open to devilish at ack.
The Five Elements smash the woods of contemplation; When the wind blows it is bound to be cold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 42</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/43/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/43/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 42 The Great Sage Reverently Visits the Southern Sea Guanyin in Her Mercy Binds the Red Boy
The story tel s how the six warriors left the cave and headed Southwest.
Monkey thought, &amp;ldquo;They are going to invite the Old King to eat our master.
I&amp;rsquo;m sure he must be the Bul Demon King. In the old days we got on very wel and were the best of friends, but now I&amp;rsquo;ve gone straight and he&amp;rsquo;s stil an evil monster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 43</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/44/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/44/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 43 At the Black River a Monster Carries Of the Priest The Dragon Prince of the West Captures an Al igator The story tel how the Bodhisat va recited the spel several times before stopping. Only then did the evil spirit&amp;rsquo;s agony cease. When he recovered, stood up and looked at himself he found that he had gold bands rounds his neck, hands and feet. They were painful y tight, and try as he would he could not move them at al .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 44</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/45/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/45/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 44 Evil in the Heart&amp;rsquo;s Centre Crosses
the Backbone Pass
There is a poem that goes:
They travel West escaping dangers to seek the scriptures; Nor can they stop at al the famous mountains.
They press on night and day, starting crows and hares; The seasons turn amid fal ing blossom and bird-song.
In the dust under one&amp;rsquo;s eyes are three thousand worlds; Four hundred prefectures rest on the head of a staff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 45</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/46/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/46/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 45 In the Hal of the Three Pure Ones the Great Sage Leaves His Name In the Kingdom of Tarrycart the Monkey King Shows His Powers The story tel s how the Great Sage Monkey pinched Friar Sand with his left hand and Pig with his right. The two of them realized what was happening and sat there on high, their heads bowed in silence, while the Taoists lit their lamps and shone them al around as they searched.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 46</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/47/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/47/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 46 False Faith Oppresses the True Dharma
The Sage Mind-Ape Eliminates Evil
The story tel s how when the king saw that Monkey had the power to summon dragons and order gods about he put his seal on the passports and handed them to the Tang Priest, whom he al owed to continue on his journey West. The three Taoist masters were so terrified that they prostrated themselves in the Hal of Golden Bel s and submit ed a memorial to the king, who came down from his dragon throne, helped them to their feet with his own hand, and said, &amp;ldquo;Why are you performing this obeisance to me today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 47</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/48/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/48/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 47 The Holy Monk Is Stopped by the River of Heaven at Night Metal and Wood in Their Mercy Rescue a Child The king col apsed on his throne in tears and cried til nightfal . Then Monkey stepped forward and cal ed out, &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t be so sil y. Look at those Taoists&amp;rsquo;bodies. One was a tiger and the other was a deer.Antelope Power was an antelope. If you don&amp;rsquo;t believe me, have his bones fished out and take a look at them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 48</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/49/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/49/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 48 A Devilish Blizzard Makes the Snow Whirl
The Monk Who Seeks to Worship Buddha Walks on Ice The story tel s how the believers in Chen Vil age noisily carried Monkey and Pig with pork, mut on, beef and wine straight to the Temple of Miraculous Response, where they set them al out with the young boy and girl in the most prominent place. Monkey looked around and saw that the offertory tables were covered with fragrant flowers and wax candles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 49</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/50/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/50/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 49 Sanzang&amp;rsquo;s Great Misfortune Is to Fal into the River Guanyin&amp;rsquo;s Fish Basket Saves the Tang Priest The story tel s how the Great Sage Monkey took his leave of the old Chen brothers, went with Pig and Friar Sand to the bank of the river, and told the two of them to decide which of them would go into the water first. &amp;ldquo;Brother,&amp;rdquo;
said Pig, &amp;ldquo;you should go first; neither of us two has very special powers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 50</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/51/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/51/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 50 Feelings Run Wild and Nature Gets Loose Because of Desire In Confusion of Spirit the Heart Is Disturbed and the Demon Encountered The poem goes:
The heart must be frequently swept,
The dust of emotions removed,
Lest the Buddha be trapped in the pit.
Only when the essence is pure
Can the origin then be discussed.
Trim the candle of nature,
Breathe in the way that Master Caoxi taught,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 51</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/52/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/52/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 51 795 In Vain Does the Mind-Ape Use a Thousand Tricks Fire and Water Fail to Harm the Demon
The story tel s how the Great Sage Equaling Heaven went empty-handed and beaten to sit down behind Mount Jindou, tears streaming from both eyes.
&amp;ldquo;Master,&amp;rdquo; he cal ed out, &amp;ldquo;I had hoped
As Lord Buddha graciously brought us together To go on to live with you, Master, for ever,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 52</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/53/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/53/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 52 Monkey Makes Havoc in the Jindou Cave
The Buddha Gives a Hint About the Owner
The story tel s how after recovering his gold-banded cudgel Monkey fought his way out of the cave and jumped up to the peak to see al the gods. He was very pleased with himself. &amp;ldquo;How did it go this time?&amp;rdquo; asked Heavenly King Li. &amp;ldquo;I did a transformation and went into the cave,&amp;rdquo; said Monkey, &amp;ldquo;where I saw the devils dancing, singing and drinking to celebrate their victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 53</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/54/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/54/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 53 The Dhyana Master Conceives after Eating a Meal The Yel ow-Wife Brings Waster to Remove a Devil Foetus Eight hundred kinds of virtue must be cultivated, Three thousand good deeds must be secretly performed.
Do not distinguish objects from self, or friend from foe: That conforms with the teaching of the Western Heaven.
The rhinoceros demon feared no weapons;
No blame at ached to the failure of water and fire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 54</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/55/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/55/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 54 The Buddha-Nature Traveling West Enters Womankind The Mind-Ape Makes a Plan to Escape from the Beauties When Sanzang and his disciples left the cot age they headed West, and about a dozen miles later they entered the country of Western Liang. &amp;ldquo;Wukong,&amp;rdquo;
said the Tang Priest on his horse, &amp;ldquo;there is a city not far ahead, and I can hear a great hubbub of voices from the marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 55</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/56/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/56/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 55 The Tang Priest Is Tempted with Sex and Debauchery Because His Nature Is Upright He Resists Unharmed The story tel s how the Great Sage and Pig were just about to use their magic to immobilize al the women when they suddenly heard the noise of a wind.
Friar Sand, who was shouting, looked round at once to find the Tang Priest gone.
&amp;ldquo;Who&amp;rsquo;s taken the master?&amp;rdquo; Monkey asked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 56</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/57/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/57/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 56 The Spirit Goes Wild and Wipes Out the Bandits The Way in Confusion Sends the Mind-Ape Away As the poem goes,
The heart that is empty of al things is said to be pure, In ut er placidity not giving rise to a thought.
The ape and the horse must be tethered, not left to run wild; The spirit must always be cautious, not seeking for glory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 57</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/58/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/58/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 57 The True Sun Wukong Makes His Complaint at Potaraka The False Monkey King Copies a Document in the Water Curtain Cave Angry and depressed, the Great Sage Sun rose up into the air. There were many places he would have liked to go to but could not. In the Water Curtain Cave on the Mountain of Flowers and Fruit he was afraid of being teased for coming back so soon after he had gone, not like a real man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 58</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/59/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/59/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 58 Two Minds Throw Heaven and Earth into Uproar One Body Cannot Achieve True Nirvana
When Monkey and Friar Sand took their leave of the Bodhisat va they departed from the Southern Ocean by two beams of auspicious light. Now Monkey&amp;rsquo;s somersault cloud was much faster than Friar Sand&amp;rsquo;s immortal&amp;rsquo;s cloud, so Monkey was drawing ahead when Friar Sand pul ed him back and said, &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s no need for you to show me your heels like that, brother, rushing ahead to sort things out at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 59</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/60/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/60/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 59 Sanzang&amp;rsquo;s Way Is Blocked at the Fiery Mountains Monkey First Tries to Borrow the Plantain Fan The many species are at root the same;
Al flows into the boundless sea.
Every thought and worry is in vain;
Al types and forms together blend.
When the achievement is complete
Great wil be the ful and shining dharma.
Do not al ow your differences to divide:
Keep everything together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 60</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/61/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/61/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 60 The Bul Demon King Gives Up the Fight to Go to a Feast Monkey Tries the Second Time to Borrow the Plantain Fan
&amp;ldquo;The Strongarm King is the Bul Demon King,&amp;rdquo; the local god explained.
&amp;ldquo;Did he set these mountains ablaze and pretend they were the Fiery Mountains?&amp;rdquo; Monkey asked.
&amp;ldquo;No, no,&amp;rdquo; the local god replied. &amp;ldquo;If you&amp;rsquo;l promise to forgive me for doing so, Great Sage, I&amp;rsquo;l speak frankly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 61</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/62/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/62/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 61 Zhu Bajie Helps to Defeat a Demon King
Monkey&amp;rsquo;s Third At empt to Borrow the Fan
The story tel s how the Bul Demon King caught up with the Great Sage Sun and saw him looking very cheerful as he went along with the plantain fan over his shoulder. &amp;ldquo;So the macaque has also tricked the art of using the fan out of her,&amp;rdquo; the demon king thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 62</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/63/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/63/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 62 Cleansed and with a Washed Heart He Sweeps the Pagoda The Devils Are Captured and Converted; the Body Is Cultivated Through al the hours it must never be forgot en: When success is won al time wil be put away.
For five years and sixty thousand miles
Do not let the holy water dry up,
Do not al ow the fire to flag.
When water and fire are in balance no harm wil arise; The Five Elements are joined as if with hooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 63</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/64/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/64/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 63 Two Monks Wipe out the Demons in the Dragon Palace The Sages Destroy Evil and Recover the Treasure The story tel s how the king of Jisai and his officials high and low watched as the Great Sage Monkey and Pig disappeared by wind and cloud, carrying 983
the two demons with them. Then al of them bowed in homage to heaven, saying, &amp;ldquo;Their fame is wel founded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 64</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/65/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/65/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 64 Wuneng Works Hard on Thorn Ridge
Sanzang Talks of Poetry in the Wood Immortals&amp;rsquo;Hermitage The story has been told how the king of Jisai thanked Tang Sanzang and his three disciples for capturing the demons and pressed on them gold and jade, none of which they would accept. The king therefore told his aides to have made for each of them two suits of clothing like those they were wearing, two pairs of socks, two pairs of shoes and two belts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 65</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/66/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/66/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 65 A Demon Creates a False Thunder Peak
Al Four Pilgrims Meet with Disaster
The cause and effect this time revealed
Should make one do what&amp;rsquo;s good and shun the evil.
Once a thought is born
The Intel igence is aware of it.
And lets it become action.
1015
Why strive to learn stupidity or skil ?
Both are medicines for heartlessness.
Do what is right while you are stil alive;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 66</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/67/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/67/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 66 Al the Gods Meet a Vicious Foe
Maitreya Binds the Evil Monster
The story tel s how the Great Sage Sun, finding himself at his wit&amp;rsquo;s end, somersaulted by auspicious cloud straight to Mount Wudang in the Southern Continent of Jambu to ask the Heavenly Honoured Demon Suppressor to save Sanzang, Pig, Friar Sand, the heavenly soldiers and al the rest of them.
He flew non-stop and was soon in sight of the patriarch&amp;rsquo;s immortal domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 67</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/68/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/68/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 67 The Dhyana-Nature Is Stable and Tuoluo Vil age Is Saved The Mind of the Way Is Purified As Corruption Is Removed The story tel s how Sanzang and his three disciples happily continued along their way after leaving the Lesser Western Heaven. They had been going for over a month, and it was now late spring. The flowers were in bloom and al the woods they could see were ful of green shade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 68</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/69/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/69/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 68 In the Land of Purpuria the Tang Priest Discusses History Sun the Pilgrim in His Charity Of ers to Be a Doctor When good is right al causes disappear;
Its fame is spread through al four continents.
In the light of wisdom they climb the other shore; Soughing dark clouds are blown from the edge of the sky.
Al the Buddhas give them help,
Sit ing for ever on their thrones of jade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 69</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/70/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/70/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 69 The Heart&amp;rsquo;s Master Prepares Medicine in the Night The Monarch Discusses a Demon at the Banquet The story tel s how the Great Sage Sun went with the eunuchs in at endance on the king to the inner quarters of the palace and stood outside the doors of the royal bed-chamber. Handing the three golden threads to the eunuchs to take inside he gave them these instructions: &amp;ldquo;Tel the queens and consorts of the inner palace or the eunuchs in personal at endance to fasten these threads to His Majesty&amp;rsquo;s left wrist at the inch, the bar and the cubit, then pass them out of the window to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 70</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/71/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/71/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 70 The Evil Monster&amp;rsquo;s Treasures Emit Smoke,
Sand and Fire Wukong Steals the Golden Bel s by Trickery The story tel s how Brother Monkey summoned up his divine prestige and rose up into the air on his magic light, wielding his iron cudgel. &amp;ldquo;Where are you from, evil monster?&amp;rdquo; he asked, shouting in the evil spirit&amp;rsquo;s face. &amp;ldquo;And where are you going to wreak havoc?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m the vanguard warrior under the Great King Evil Star Matcher from Horndog Cave on Mount Unicorn,&amp;rdquo; shouted the demon at the top of his voice,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 71</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/72/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/72/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 71 Under a False Name Monkey Beats the Demon Hound Guanyin Appears to Subdue the Demon King
Mat er has always been empty;
Emptiness said to be mat er is only natural.
When one penetrates the dhyana of mat er&amp;rsquo;s emptiness There is no need for cinnabar to be refined into elixir.
Rest not when pursuing perfection of virtue and conduct; Endure suffering to achieve hard-won skil s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 72</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/73/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/73/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 72 The Seven Emotions Confuse the Basic in Gossamer Cave At Filth-Cleansing Spring Pig Forgets Himself The story tel s how Sanzang took his leave of the king of Purpuria, got everything ready, saddled the horse and headed Westwards. They crossed many a mountain and river. Before they realized it autumn and winter were over and spring&amp;rsquo;s brightness and charm were back. Master and disciples were enjoying the scenery as their way led them across the greenery when they suddenly noticed a building amid trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 73</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/74/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/74/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 73 The Emotions Bear a Grudge and Inflict Disaster The Heart&amp;rsquo;s Master Smashes the Light When He Meets the Demons The story tel s how the Great Sage Sun supported the Tang Priest as they hurried along the main road to the West together with Pig and Friar Sand.
Within a few hours they were in sight of a compound with many tal towers and imposing buildings. &amp;ldquo;Disciple,&amp;rdquo; said Sanzang, reining in his horse,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 74</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/75/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/75/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 74 Li Changgeng Reports the Demons&amp;rsquo;Vicious Nature The Novice Displays His Powers of Transformation Emotions and desires are in origin al the same; Both emotions and desires are completely natural.
Many a gentleman refines himself in the Buddhist faith; When desire and emotions are forgot en, dhyana conies.
Don&amp;rsquo;t be impatient; be firm of heart;
Be free of dust like the moon in the sky.
Make no mistake in your labors and your progress; When your efforts are completed you wil be an enlightened immortal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 75</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/76/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/76/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 75 The Mind-Ape Bores a Hole in the Male and Female Jar 1178
The Demon King Returns and the Way Is Preserved The story tel s how the Great Sage Sun went in through the entrance of the cave and looked to either side. This is what he saw: Hil s of skeletons,
Forests of bones,
Human heads and hair trampled into felt,
Human skin and flesh rot ed into mud,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 76</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/77/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/77/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 76 When the Heart Spirit Stays in the Home the Demons Submit The Mother of Wood Helps Bring Monsters to the Truth The story tel s how after the Great Sage had struggled in his stomach for a while the senior demon col apsed in the dust. He made no sound and was not breathing either. As he said nothing Monkey thought the demon was dead, so he stopped hit ing him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 77</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/78/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/78/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 77 The Demon Host Mistreats the Fundamental Nature The One Body Pays His Respects to the Buddha We wil tel now not of the sufferings of the venerable Tang Elder but of the three demon chiefs in strenuous combat with the Great Sage and his two brother disciples in the low hil s to the East outside the city. It was indeed a good hard bat le, like an iron brush against a copper pan: Six types of body, six types of weapon,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 78</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/79/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/79/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 78 In Bhiksuland the Hidden Gods Are Sent on an Errand of Mercy In the Palace the Monster Is Revealed and the Way Discussed A single thought at once disturbs a hundred monsters; The hardest efforts are al to no avail.
One can only wash away each speck of dust,
Tidy everything and polish wel .
Sweep al causation away and come to nirvana;
Waste no time and destroy the thousand demons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 79</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/80/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/80/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 79 Searching the Cave to Capture the Fiend They Meet Longevity The Reigning Monarch Saves the Lit le Boys The story tel s how the royal aide dragged the imitation Tang Priest out of the government hostel and marched him, heavily surrounded by royal guardsmen, straight to the gates of the palace, where he said to the eunuch gate officer, &amp;ldquo;Please be so good as to report to His Majesty that we have brought the Tang Priest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 80</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/81/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/81/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 80 The Young Girl Seeks a Mate to Build Up the Male Protecting His Master the Mind-Ape Sees Through a Demon The story tel s how the king, ministers and common people of Bhiksuland escorted the Tang Priest and his three disciples out of the city. Seven miles later they were stil unwil ing to part from the pilgrims, but Sanzang insisted on get ing out of the coach, mounting the horse and taking his leave of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 81</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/82/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/82/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 81 The Mind-Ape Recognizes a Monster in the Monastery The Three Search for Their Master in Black Pine Forest The story tel s how Sanzang and his disciples came to the Meditation Monastery where they met the lamas and were given a vegetarian meal.
When the four of them had eaten the girl was also fed. By now night was gradual y fal ing and the lamp was lit in the abbot&amp;rsquo;s lodgings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 82</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/83/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/83/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 82 The Girl Seeks the Male The Primal Deity Guards the Way
The story tel s how Pig leapt down the mountainside and found a narrow path.After fol owing it for nearly two miles he came across two she-monsters drawing water from a wel . How did he know that they both were monsters?
Each of them had on her head an extremely unfashionable hair-style held up 1293</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 83</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/84/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/84/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 83 The Mind-Ape Recognizes the Refiner of Cinnabar The Girl Reverts to Her True Nature
The story tel s how after Sanzang had been carried out of the cave by the evil spirit Friar Sand went up to him and asked, &amp;ldquo;Where is my oldest brother now that you have come out, Master?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;He must know what he&amp;rsquo;s doing,&amp;rdquo; said Pig. &amp;ldquo;I expect he&amp;rsquo;s exchanged himself for the master to get him out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 84</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/85/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/85/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 84 The Indestructible Proteges of the Buddha Complete Enlightenment The Dharma King Comes to the Truth Through His Own Nature The story tel s how Tang Sanzang kept his masculine essence intact and escaped from the terrible snare of mist and flowers.As he headed Westwards with Brother Monkey he did not notice that it was already summer: warm breezes were beginning to blow, and the early summer rain was fal ing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 85</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/86/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/86/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 85 The Mind-ape is jealous of the Mother of Wood The Demon Chief Plots to Devour the Master of Dhyana The story tel s how when the king held his dawn audience the civil and military officials al carried memorials. &amp;ldquo;Sovereign Lord,&amp;rdquo; they reported, &amp;ldquo;we beg you to forgive your servants for their lack of decorum.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Gentlemen,&amp;rdquo; the king replied, &amp;ldquo;you are al as courteous as ever. What lack 1341</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 86</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/87/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/87/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 86 The Mother of Wood Lends His Might in Defeating the Ogre The Metal Lord Uses His Magic to Wipe Out the Monster The story tel s how the Great Sage Monkey was leading the horse and carrying the baggage while he searched the whole mountain top, cal ing out for his master. Suddenly Pig came running up to him, puffing and panting, to ask, &amp;ldquo;Why are you shouting like that, brother?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 87</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/88/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/88/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 87 When Heaven Is Of ended in Fengxian It Stops the Rain The Great Sage Urges Goodness and Brings a Downpour Deep and mysterious is the Great Way;
What news is there of it?
When revealed it wil alarm ghosts and divine beings.
It controls the universe,
Divides darkness and light;
In the world of true happiness there is no competition.
Before the Vulture Peak
Pearls and jewels emerge,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 88</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/89/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/89/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 88 When the Dhyana Reaches Yuhua a Display of Magic Is Given The Mind-Ape and the Mother of Wood Take Their Own Disciples The story tel s how after happily taking their leave of the marquis the Tang Priest turned to Monkey as he rode and said, &amp;ldquo;Worthy disciple, this good result was even bet er than rescuing the babies in Bhiksuland, and it was al your achievement.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 89</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/90/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/90/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 89 The Tawny Lion Spirit Arranges a Rake Feast in Vain Metal, Wood and Earth Make Havoc on Mount Leopard Head The story tel s how after days on end of hard work the smiths al went to sleep that night, only to get up at dawn to start again and find that the three weapons had disappeared from under the mat ing shelter. Dumbfounded with horror, they started looking for them everywhere, and when the three young princes came out of the inner quarters to watch, the smiths al kowtowed to them and said, &amp;ldquo;Young masters, we don&amp;rsquo;t know where the divine teachers&#39;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 90</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/91/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/91/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 90 By Giving and Receiving the Master and the Lion Turn into One After Stealing the Way and Obstructing Dhyana Ninefold Numinosity Is Pacified
The story tel s how the Great Sage Sun left the city with Pig and Friar Sand and looked the monsters in the face to see that they were al lions of various kinds. The Tawny Lion Spirit was leading, with Leo and Elephant-fighter Lion on his left, Gryphon and Raccoon-dog Lion on his right and Monkey Lion with Snowy Lion behind him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 91</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/92/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/92/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 91 Admiring the Moon Festival Lanterns in Jinping The Tang Priest Confesses in Dark Essence Cave Where should one strive to practice dhyana?
Swiftly to extirpate the misdeeds of the thought-horse and the mind-ape.
When they are firmly tethered they give off radiance, But whoever halts fal s to the three paths of suffering.
If one al ows the divine elixir to leak away, The jade-pure nature wil wither as one slackens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 92</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/93/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/93/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 92 Three Monks Wage a Great Fight on Green Dragon Mountain Four Stars Seize the Rhinoceros Monsters
The story tel s how after the Great Sage Monkey took his two brother disciples by gale and cloud to the Northeast they were soon bringing their cloud down at the entrance to the Dark Essence Cave on Green Dragon Mountain. Pig was just about to smash the doors in when Monkey said, &amp;ldquo;Wait a moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 93</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/94/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/94/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 93 In the Almsgiver&amp;rsquo;s Garden Antiquity and Causes Are Discussed In the Court of India the King Meets the Monks When thoughts arise there surely wil be desire, Longing is certain to lead one to disaster.
Why should intel igence distinguish the three ranks of nobility?
When conduct is complete it natural y returns to the primal sea.
Whether you become an immortal or a Buddha,
Al must be arranged from within.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 94</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/95/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/95/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 94 The Four Monks Dine to Music in the Palace Gardens One Demon Loves in Vain and Longs for Bliss The story tel s how Brother Monkey and the other two disciples went with the official who had brought the invitation to outside the Meridional Gate of the palace, where the eunuch gate officer immediately reported their arrival and brought back a summons for them to enter. The three of them stood in a row, not bowing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 95</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/96/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/96/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 95 False and True Form Combine When the Jade Hare is Captured The True Female Is Converted and Meets With Spiritual Origin The story tel s how the Tang Priest was feeling thoroughly miserable as he accompanied the king into the inner quarters, from where a great sound of drums and music arose and fine perfumes could be smelt. He kept his head bowed, not daring to look up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 96</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/97/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/97/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 96 Squire Kou Entertains the Lofty Monk
The Tang Priest Does Not Covet Wealth and Honour Al kinds of mat er are real y without mat er; No emptiness is truly empty.
Stil ness and clamour, speech and silence, al are the same: Why bother to dream-talk in one&amp;rsquo;s dreams?
The useful includes the useless in its application; Achievement lurks within failure.
When the fruit is ripe it reddens of itself;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 97</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/98/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/98/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 97 The Monks and Their Supporters Meet With Demonic At ack The Sage Makes the Spirit Reappear to Save the Primal One We wil tel not of how the Tang Priest and the others endured a hard night in the dilapidated palace of Padmaprabha, but of a group of evil vil ains in Diling county in the prefecture of Brazentower who had squandered al their families&amp;rsquo; fortunes in whoring, drinking and gambling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 98</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/99/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/99/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 98 When the Ape and the Horse Are Tamed They Cast Of Their Husks When Al the Deeds Have Been Done Reality Is Seen The story told how after coming back to life Mr. Kou once more arranged for parasols, banners, drummers, musicians, Buddhist monks, Taoist priests, his friends and his relations to see Sanzang off again. But instead of describing this we wil tel of the Tang Priest and his three disciples taking the main road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 99</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/100/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/100/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 99 When the Nine Nines Are Complete the Demons Are Al Destroyed After the Triple Threes Are Fulfil ed the Way Returns to Its Roots The story goes on to tel how the Eight Vajrapanis escorted the Tang Priest back to their country, but we wil not go into that now.
Outside the gates the Protectors of the Four Quarters and the Centre, the Four Duty Gods, the Six Dings, the Six Jias and the Guardians of the Faith went up to the Bodhisat va Guanyin and said, &amp;ldquo;We, your disciples, have given secret help to the holy monk in obedience to your dharma command, Bodhisat va.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 100</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/101/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:45:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Journey-to-the-West/101/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 100 The Journey Back to the East Is Made
The Five Immortals Achieve Nirvana
We wil tel not of how the four travelers escaped and rose on the wind with the vajrapanis, but of the many people in the Temple of Deliverance in Chen Vil age. After they rose at dawn to prepare more fruit and delicacies to offer they came to the ground floor of the tower and found the Tang Priest gone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
