<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LiteraryLark</title>
    <link>https://literarylark.com/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/</link>
    <description>Recent content on LiteraryLark</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 21:41:18 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://literarylark.com/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prologue</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 21:41:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/0/</guid>
      <description>A planet teeming with advanced life rotates in the vast and boundless cosmos. The planet&amp;rsquo;s sole advanced lifeform refers to itself as humans!
Awakening from primitive times, evolving over countless millions of years, and passing through three consecutive mythological eras - &amp;ldquo;Worship of Gods,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Demise of Gods,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Creation of Gods&amp;rdquo; - humans entered a new era. They abandoned the primitive and mysterious myths, grasping the weapon of &amp;ldquo;science.&amp;rdquo; They severed the instinctual power clinging to them, stepping into a new age of enlightenment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1, Su Yi, Episode 1, Episode 1</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 21:41:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Zhenyu, hurry, go&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ll hold him back, you go!&amp;rdquo; Senior Jingyuan shouted loudly to me.
&amp;ldquo;With your martial arts skills, you won&amp;rsquo;t stand a chance&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Get out of here!&amp;rdquo;
The door was rammed open, and I stumbled out, the sound of gunfire erupting behind me. The door, now riddled with bullet holes from the ricochets, indicated that Senior Jingyuan&amp;rsquo;s martial arts skills were indeed lacking. He wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be able to stop my crazed father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 1 Episode 1 Rampage Languang Chapter 2 Sister</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 21:41:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/2/</guid>
      <description>Languang Seven Islands, located just a few dozen nautical miles from the largest continent of the Eastern Midland Plate, are inhabited by people of the Yanhuang ethnic group. They are a group of picturesque islands in the vast Heavenly Ocean, often referred to as the &amp;ldquo;earrings of the Heavenly Ocean.&amp;rdquo;
Originally, these islands were known for producing a precious gemstone called &amp;ldquo;blue light,&amp;rdquo; and were referred to as &amp;ldquo;Languang&amp;rdquo; by ancient people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3 You Rong</title>
      <link>https://literarylark.com/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 21:41:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://literarylark.com/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/3/</guid>
      <description>Little did I know of a conspiracy conversation going on in sync with me, I only know one thing now - I&amp;rsquo;m lost!
Turning left and right, I obviously saw the government building opposite the Spring and Autumn Pavilion, but why did I walk further and further away? I was really baffled, after half an hour of being in a daze, the pedestrians were much denser at dusk, and the crowds were mixed, so my cloth bag was so light, and my wallet flew away!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
