<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eternal Hero in a World of Demises on Geekdocs</title>
    <link>http://example.org/eternal-hero-in-a-world-of-demise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eternal Hero in a World of Demises on Geekdocs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 21:41:18 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/eternal-hero-in-a-world-of-demise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>0</title>
      <link>http://example.org/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 21:41:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/0/</guid>
      <description>Prologue A planet with advanced life revolves in the vast and boundless universe. The only group of advanced life on the planet calls itself human beings!
Awakening from the primitive age, time has evolved over tens of millions of years, and after three consecutive mythological ages of &amp;ldquo;worshiping gods&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;destroying gods&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;creating gods&amp;rdquo;, human beings have entered a new era. Leaving aside, human beings grasped the sharp weapon of &amp;ldquo;science&amp;rdquo;, cut off the power of instinct absorbed in them, and stepped into a new era of high development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1</title>
      <link>http://example.org/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 21:41:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/1/</guid>
      <description>Chapter 1, Su Yi, Episode 1, Episode 1 &amp;ldquo;Brother Zhenyu, let&amp;rsquo;s go&amp;hellip;I&amp;rsquo;m stopping him, let&amp;rsquo;s go!&amp;rdquo; Brother Jingyuan shouted to me.
&amp;ldquo;Just relying on your triangular cat&amp;rsquo;s kung fu&amp;hellip; Get out!&amp;rdquo;
The door was knocked open, and I staggered out of the door. Gunshots rang out from behind, and the door that bounced back was battered.
Kong, it seems that senior brother Jingyuan&amp;rsquo;s kung fu is really not good enough, he will definitely not be able to stop my crazy dad!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The last hero 2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 21:41:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/2/</guid>
      <description>Part 1 Episode 1 Rampage Languang Chapter 2 Sister The Languang Seven Islands are separated from the largest Zhongtianzhou continental plate in the east by only a few dozen sea miles. The residents on it belong to the Yanhuang ethnic group. &amp;ldquo;The name.
The island group was originally rich in a kind of precious sapphire, so it was called &amp;ldquo;Blue Light&amp;rdquo; by the ancients. However, due to climate change in the past thousand years, the island group has become a prosperous production area of many rare orchid varieties, so it was renamed &amp;ldquo;Blue Light&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The last hero 3</title>
      <link>http://example.org/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 21:41:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/Eternal-Hero-in-a-World-of-Demise/3/</guid>
      <description>Chapter 3 You Rong Little did I know of a conspiracy conversation going on in sync with me, I only know one thing now - I&amp;rsquo;m lost!
Turning left and right, I obviously saw the government building opposite the Spring and Autumn Pavilion, but why did I walk further and further away? I was really baffled, after half an hour of being in a daze, the pedestrians were much denser at dusk, and the crowds were mixed, so my cloth bag was so light, and my wallet flew away!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
